Finding Aid for the Barbara and Willard Morgan photographs and papers LSC.2278
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 8: Barbara Morgan personal and biographical materials, 1938-2004
  - Subseries 8.1: Articles, interviews, oral histories, 1941-2004
    - Wille, Alicia - book project, 1975-1978 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - WNYC - The Changing World of Women with Phyllis Sanders, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Women of Vision: Photographic Statements by Twenty Women Photographers, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Women, Photography, and the Art Establishment: How Far Have We Come - symposium address, 1990-1992 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - WQXR - The World of Dance With Frances Mason, 1994, 2001, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Other articles, 1972-1994 (Box 97, Folder 12)
      Articles about Barbara Morgan and interviews with Morgan
      "Barbara Morgan: Inner Dialogues With the External World", in Quadrille, Vol. 5 No. 4, Bennington College, Summer 1971.
      Berg, Gretchen, "Barbara Morgan The Delight-Maker: An interview by Gretchen Berg", pp. 1-24, and Sue Turconi, "Women Vision", p. in The PWP Times (Professional Women Photographers), Spring 1982.
      Goldberg, Vicki, "Transfixing Motion and Emotion in a Shutter's Blink", in New York Times, March 14, 1999.
      Kirkpatrick, Diane, "Barbara Morgan and 20-th Century Photography", in East Quad Symposium-Museum of Art Exhibition & Performance, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor exhibition catalog, September 21, 1992. Reprinted by Willard & Barbara Morgan Archives.
      McCausland, Elizabeth, "Barbara Morgan Photographs The Dance" in Minicam Photography, March, [year] reprinted by The Willard & Barbara Morgan Archives, undated.
      Papier, Deborah, "All the Atoms are Dancing", in Washington Calendar Magazine, October 1976.
      Robin Holland, Robin, "An Interview with Barbara Morgan: A Life in Movement", in Darkroom Photography, Volume Three Number Five, September 1981. pp. 38-41; 44, 47, 49, 50.
      Soares, Janet, "Barbara Morgan" in The R. Levine Distinguished Artist Series & The Barnard College Dance Faculty exhibition catalog, American Modern Dance: 1935-1945. Highlights of Dance Productions by Martha Graham, Doris Humphrey & Charles Weidman, February 11, 1991.
      Spencer, Ruth, "Barbara Morgan", in The British Journal of Photography, June 13, 1975.
      Szarkowski, John, "Barbara Morgan", in Looking at photographs: 100 pictures from the collection of the Museum of Modern Art, pp. 136-137. The Museum of Modern Art, 1973.
      Also includes a 1983 film program of The American Federation of Arts.
    - Published articles about Barbara Morgan, 1935-1995 (Box 410, Folders 7-9)
      Folder 9 includes drafts by William Agee and Curtis Carter for Barbara Morgan: prints, drawings, watercolors & photographs / Patrick & Beatrice Haggerty Museum of Art, Marquette University, 1988.
    - Unpublished interviews and related documents, 1980-1982 (Box 97, Folder 13)
      Unpublished interviews are by Lloyd Morgan and Caitlin M., Sherilyn Brandenstein and one unidentified interviewer. Also includes Lloyd Morgan's Talk on Barbara Morgan at Bennington and notes regarding other interviews with Morgan.
    - Dictation transcripts, 1928, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Oral history - UCLA, 1971-1990 (Box 98, Folders 1-4)
    - Oral history - UCLA: notes and preparation, circa 1970s (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Oral history - UCLA: Annita Delano, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Oral history - University of Wisconsin, 1975 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Oral History - Arts at Black Mountain College, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Oral history - Columbia University, 1979, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Oral history - New York Public Library, 1985 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1920s-2000s (Box 100)
  - Subseries 8.2: Biographical writing, 1961-1996
    Morgan's autobiographical writings, including drafts and final copies of personal statements and chronologies.
    - Biographical reference books, 1968-1973, 1996 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Biography material, circa 1970s (Box 101, Folders 2-3)
    - Biography material - childhood influences, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Biography material - for CV, circa 1960-1980 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Biography material - southwest overflow/exploring, circa 1961 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Biographical info to send, circa 1980 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Biography - chronology master list for updates, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Personal biographical background for photographic record, circa 1960s (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Chronology, circa 1980 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Chronology - drafts, 1971 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Chronology - new edition, 1971 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Personal biographical statements, 1975 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 8.3: Personal materials, 1938-1999
    Personal items and documentation of Morgan's major life events and achievements, including awards, her schoolwork and yearbooks from Pomona High School; travel ephemera, and obituaries and tributes.
    - 90th birthday celebration - invitation and planning, 1990 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Awards - 38th Annual Capezio Dance Award, 1989 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Awards - American Society of Magazine Photographers Lifetime Achievement, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Awards - Dinner for Martha Graham, White House, 1976 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Awards - First International Photographic Exhibition, 1938 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Awards - Marquette University Honorary Degree, 1977-1978 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Awards - Park West Camera Club, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Awards - Photographic InSight Foundation, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Awards - Society of Photographic Education, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Awards - Town of Greenburgh, New York: Barbara Morgan Day, 1984 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Awards - UCLA Alumni Association Golden Bruin Award, 1981 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Awards - Women's Caucus for Art Honor Award, 1986 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Awards - other, 1952-1991 (Box 128, Folder 9, Box 188, Folder 2)
    - High school friends - photographs, 1916 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Passports and Identifications, 1950s-1970s (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Poetry written for Barbara Morgan, 1950-1982 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Pomona High School papers, 1917-1919 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Pomona High School yearbooks, 1914-1920 (Box 149, Folders 5-8)
    - Teaching credentials, 1923 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Travel - Europe: itinerary, 1954 (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Travel - Europe: Spain, Italy, Greece, France, England, 1959 (Box 149, Folders 11-14)
    - Travel - Europe: Crete, Lascaux, 1959 (Box 150, Folders 1-4)
    - Travel - Europe: photographs (slides), 1959 (Box 217)
    - Travel - Mexico, South America, circa 1966 (Box 150, Folders 5-7)
    - Obituaries, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Tribute - speeches and transcripts, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Tribute - invitation, planning, guest book, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Tribute - message and photograph of Barbara, 1992 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Sympathy letters, 1992-1993 (Box 129, Folders 4-7)
    - Vital documents, 1930s-1990s (Box 149, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 8.4: Calendars and telephone directories, 1940s-1980s
    Calendars and phone books kept by Morgan over the years, containing appointments and contacts related to her personal and professional life.
    - Calendars, 1955-1972 (Box 130)
    - Telephone directories, 1940s-1970s (Box 131)
    - Rolodex A-Z; name and subject cards; quotes, 1970s-1980s (Box 132, Box 133, Box 134)
    - Rolodex, 1970s (Box 135)
- Series 9: Barbara Morgan photographic material, 1920s-2000s; Negative numbers are written on many of the photographic prints and contact prints. Some prints are signed, stamped, or have labels crediting Barbara Morgan. Many unmounted prints have notations on the back, such as numbers or the lowercase and uppercase letters A or NA. The numbers generally refer to Morgan publication page numbers and the prints with an A or NA indicate whether or not they were printed archivally and were likely printed during Barbara's lifetime. When Morgan started printing archivally using Ansel Adams's method (see Subseries 3.2: "Permanence" files), she marked everything done prior to the official "archival" printing method. Prints on glossy or single weight paper are likely work prints or for reproduction or publicity purposes (especially among the small prints).
  This series contains all formats of Barbara Morgan's art photography from raw negatives to finished, exhibition-ready prints. Included are:
  Mounted, unmounted, and matted prints, including vintage and later prints (many undated).
  Small prints used for publicity, reproduction, and other purposes (up to 8 x 10 format)
  Contact prints and contact sheets comprised of:
  Medium finished prints (up to 16 x 20 format)
  Large finished prints (over 16 x 20 format).
  Negatives (cut film and roll film), many of which are integrated with contact prints.
  Arrangement
  Most of the negatives are numbered corresponding to systems created by Morgan or by others during her lifetime.
  NOTE: To access inventories and photo date books detailing the subjects and negative numbers assigned to photographs and negatives, see Subseries 3.1 Business Records (Inventories: Box 43; and Photo Date Books: Boxes 44 and 45).
  PDF's of the original handwritten inventories and photo date books are attached:
  Barbara Morgan Negative Collection
  Photographs Taken by Barbara and Willard Morgan: 35mm and Canisters
  For the negatives and film described in this inventory, see Subseries 9.8 Roll film - negatives and contact sheets, 1960s, undated (Boxes 431, 556, 557, and 564-569).
  Negative numbers are written on many of the photographic prints and contact prints. Some prints are signed, stamped, or have labels crediting Barbara Morgan. Many unmounted prints have notations on the back, such as numbers or the lowercase and uppercase letters A or NA. The numbers generally refer to Morgan publication page numbers and the prints with an A or NA indicate whether or not they were printed archivally and were likely printed during Barbara's lifetime.
  When Morgan started printing archivally using Ansel Adams's method (see Subseries 3.2: "Permanence" files), she marked everything done prior to the official "archival" printing method as such. Prints on glossy or single weight paper are likely working prints or were for reproduction or publicity purposes (especially the small prints).
  The last section of this series (9.8 Negatives and contact prints, 1920s-1970s, undated) contains the bulk of the Morgans' files of integrated contact prints and negatives (5 x 7 and 4 x 5 formats and roll film).
  For Morgan's photography projects, such as books and photography for college campuses and schools, see Series 4: Barbara Morgan photographic projects.
  - Subseries 9.1: City photography, 1930s, undated
    This subseries contains photographic material depicting New York City--buildings, signs, street views (some photographed from overhead), and people. Some of these photographs may have been used in Barbara Morgan's photomontages.
    Photographs by Willard Morgan may also be included in this subseries. (See also Series 18: Collaborative work--Subseries 18.2: New York and other locations).
    - Photographic prints (medium), circa 1930s (Box 324, Box 325, Box 355, Box 382)
    - Photographic prints (small) and contact prints, circa 1930s, undated (Box 240, Box 426, Box 428)
      Includes New York City people and places: Madison Square Park, boats and wharves, moving cars, garage-rubble, New York City buildings, shop fronts and signs, gutters, highways, nightclubs, theaters, wrecked buildings, people on sidewalks, crowds, and Coney Island.
      Also includes Barnsdall details.
    - Negatives, 1933-1947, undated
      - Madison Square from Morgan Studio and other city photographs., 1933-1947; 5 x 7 and smaller negatives. (Box 550, Box 553)
      - New York City, 1937-1939; 4 x 5 and smaller negatives and contact prints. (Box 542)
        New York, Madison Square, architectural details, construction steel, crowds and clusters, parades, elevated railways, and traffic.
      - New York City, 1937-1948; 4 x 5 negatives and contact prints. (Box 531, Box 535)
        Madison Square Peace Meeting, car rhythms, street scenes. Also includes Germany Surrenders by Willard Morgan.
      - New York City, undated; 35mm negatives. (Box 558)
        New York City buildings and streets (by Willard Morgan ?)
      - New York City at night, 5 x 7 and smaller negatives. (Box 545)
      - New York City: Chrysler building, streets, etc., 2-1/4" and 5 x 7 negatives. (Box 546)
  - Subseries 9.2: Dance photography, 1920s-1990s, undated; 1930s-1940s
    This subseries contains Morgan's dance photography: images she took of Martha Graham and her dancers in the 1930s and 1940s, as well as other dancers from the same period. Dancers represented in photographic prints include: Valerie Bettis, Si Lan Chen, Merce Cunningham, Asadata Dafora and Lolita, Jane Dudley, Erick Hawkins, Hanya Holm, Doris Humphrey, Louise Kloepper, José Limón, Sophie Maslow, Daniel Nagrin, May O'Donnell, Pearl Primus, Anna Sokolow, Helen Tamiris, Marian Van Tuyl, and Charles Weidman. Additional dancers are represented in contact prints and negatives.
    Several subseries' in Series 4 also contain dance photography, including Barbara Morgan photographic projects, Bennington College, 1938-1939, Sarah Lawrence College, 1955-1957, and Book projects, 1930s-1997.
    - Faces of Modern Dance exhibition - photographic prints, 1920s-1990s; 1930s-1940s
      These prints comprise most of the pieces exhibited in the 2004 Marquette University exhibition, Faces of Modern Dance plus some additional dance prints that were on the preliminary exhibition checklist. Many retain their museum mats and are numbered per the exhibition checklist. Exhibition checklist numbers are indicated below in ( ) following photograph descriptions.
      The checklist and published catalog are in Box 153, Folders 4-6 (Series 1: Barbara Morgan exhibition materials--Marquette University, Faces of Modern Dance: Barbara Morgan Photographs, 2004.) Other printed material related to this exhibition is in the same series, Box 5, Folder 14.
      Numberedrints from the exhibition not present in this sub-series are listed below. Prints of these photographs may be found in Subseries 9.2 Dance - Other Dancers (medium) and Other Dancers (small) and contact prints:
      Merce Cunningham, Totem Ancestor, 1942. (25, 26, and 33).
      Pearl Primus, Rock Daniel, 1944. Gelatin silver print. Vintage-toned print, signed, mounted, printed later. 17 x 15 in. (48, 49)
      Helen Tamiris & Daniel Nagrin, Untitled, 1944. Gelatin silver print. Signed, printed 1960s-1970s. 19-3/4 x 15-1/2 in. (73)
      The Faces of Modern Dance exhibition prints are located in the following boxes:
      Boxes 385-396 - Large prints (16 x 20 format prints) with larger mats (from 18 x 22 inches up to 24 x 32 inches)
      Boxes 338-372 - Medium prints and mats (8 x 10 - 16 x 20 format prints in mats ranging from 14 x 18 to 16 x 20 inches)
      Boxes 243-244 - Small prints (4 x 5, 8 x 10 and up to 11 x 14 format prints, unmatted.)
      - Large Prints (16 x 20 format ) with larger mats (18 x 22 inches to 24 x 32 inches)
        - Valerie Bettis, The Desperate Heart, 1944; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 18 x 15 inch mat window. Some curling on edges. (29) (Box 392)
        - Valerie Bettis, The Desperate Heart, [1944]; Gelatin silver print, double exposure. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 15 x 19 inch mat window. (65) (Box 391)
        - Valerie Bettis, The Desperate Heart, (white dress, back of feet), 1944; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 15 x 20 inch mat window. (62) (Box 392)
        - Valerie Bettis, The Desperate Heart, (high kick, face not seen), 1944; Gelatin silver print. Signed, later printing. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 19 x 15 inch mat window. (64) (Box 392)
        - Valerie Bettis, The Desperate Heart, (low kick crossing front of body), 1944; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 19-1/4 x 13-1/4 inch mat window. (61) (Box 392)
        - Valerie Bettis, Prairie Born, [1944]; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 24 x 32 inches, with 15-1/4 x 9 in. mat window. (41) (Box 396)
        - Merce Cunningham, El Penitente ("Christus"), 1940; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed, mounted for reproduction and marked "p. 96"). 16 x 20 format print, trimmed, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 18 x 14-1/4 inch mat window. (44) (Box 393)
        - Merce Cunningham, Root of the Unfocus (II), 1944; Gelatin silver print, double exposure. Signed. Printed 1960s-70s. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 15-1/8 x 19-1/4 in. mat window. (50) (Box 391)
        - Merce Cunningham & Pearl Lang, 1942; Gelatin silver print. Double exposure. Signed. Archivally printed later. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 20 x 24 inches, with 15-5/8 x 13-3/8 inch mat window. (46) (Box 386)
        - Merce Cunningham, Totem Ancestor, 1942; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, trimmed and matted to 32 x 24 inches, with 16 x 19-1/4 inch mat window. (34) (Box 395)
        - Cunningham/Graham/Hawkins, El Penitente, 1940, printed ca. 1980; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 14-1/4 x 17-7/8 inch mat window. (15) (Box 393)
        - Jane Dudley, Cante Flamenco, 1942; Gelatin silver print. Vintage. 13-1/2 x 10-5/8 in. print, matted to 18 x 22 inches, with 13 x 10 inch mat window. (59) (Box 385)
        - Jane Dudley, Cante Flamenco, [1942]; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, trimmed, mounted on board, and matted to 32 x 24 inches, with 20-1/2 x 15-7/8 inch mat window. (60) (Box 395)
        - Jane Dudley, Leap #1, and Leap #2 (Box 395)
          Two prints in one mat measuring 32 x 24 inches, with two mat windows, 9 x 12 inches each.
          Top: Jane Dudley, Leap #1, (in leotard). Gelatin silver print (glossy). Vintage. (79)
          Bottom: Jane Dudley, Leap #2, (in leotard). Gelatin silver print (matte). Vintage. (80)
        - Martha Graham, American Document, (trio), (double exposure), 1938; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 18-1/2 x 15-1/4 inch mat window. (81) (Box 393)
        - Martha Graham, American Document, (trio) (double exposure), [1938]; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed, mounted. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 15 x 19-1/8 inch mat window. (31) "Graham Group" handwritten on mat. Water damage to board, streaks on photograph. (Box 393)
        - Martha Graham, Letter to the World, (Kick), 1940; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. Print is trimmed to 19-1/4 x 15-3/8 in. and mounted on board 28 x 22 in. (67) (Box 393)
        - Martha Graham & Erick Hawkins, Every Soul Is a Circus, [1940]; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 19 x 15 inch mat window. (47) (Box 393)
        - Erick Hawkins, El Penitente (Solo, "El Flagellante"), 1940; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, trimmed, mounted on board, and matted to 32 x 24 inches, with 20-3/8 x 15-3/4 inch mat window. (32) (Box 394)
        - Doris Humphrey, With My Red Fires, 1938; Gelatin silver print. Mounted estate print, embossed signature. 9-1/2 x 9-1/2 inch image on 12-7/8 x 10-1/2 paper, matted to 18 x 22 inches, with 10-1/2 x 10-1/2 inch mat window. (66) (Box 385)
        - Doris Humphrey, With My Red Fires, (seated), 1938; Gelatin silver print. Vintage. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 15-3/8 x 19-1/2 inch mat window. (77) (Box 390)
        - Doris Humphrey, Shaker, (Bea Seckler and group), 1938; Gelatin silver print, signed, printed 1960s-70s. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 15 x 19 inch mat window. (72) (Box 390)
        - Doris Humphrey, Shakers (group), 1938; Gelatin silver print, signed. 16 x 20 format print, trimmed and mounted on board, and matted to 24 x 32 inches, with 16-1/4 x 20 inch mat window. (68) (Box 394)
        - Humphrey Group, Two Dancers Leaping, (neg. 526), Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. Print trimmed to 9-1/4 x 13 inches, mounted and matted to 18 x 22 inches, with 9-1/4 x 13 inch mat window. (39) (Box 385)
        - Doris Humphrey & Weidman, Square Dance for Moderns (facing front), 1938; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 18-3/4 x 15-1/2 inch mat window. (42) (Box 390)
        - Doris Humphrey & Weidman, Square Dance for Moderns (facing back), 1938; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 18-3/8 x 15-5/8 inch mat window. (43) (Box 390)
        - Louise Kloepper, All Bennington, [1938]; Gelatin silver print. Vintage. Three 8 x 10 format prints. Three windows in one 28 x 22 inch mat: Top to bottom: 6-7/8 x 8-5/8 inches, 8-7/8 x 6-7/8 inches, and 8-7/8 x 6-7/8 inches. (51, 52, 53) (Box 391)
        - José Limón, Peon, Mexican Suite, 1944; Gelatin silver print. Signed, mounted. Printed 1960s–70s. 15 x 19-1/4 inch print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 14-7/8 x 19-1/4 inch mat window. (37) (Box 391)
        - Sophie Maslow & Bill Bales, Sweet Betsy From Pike, [1938]; Gelatin silver print, signed. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, mounted and matted with 19 x 15-1/2 inch mat window. (76) (Box 391)
        - Daniel Nagrin, [1944]; Gelatin silver print, double exposure. Signed. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 15-3/8 x 18 inch mat window. (74) (Box 391)
        - Daniel Nagrin, [1944]; Gelatin silver print, signed. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 15-1/4 x 19-1/4 inch mat window. (75) (Box 391)
        - Anna Sokolow, I Had a Garden, 1940; Gelatin silver print. Estate print. Embossed signature. 11 x 13-5/8 inch image on slightly larger paper, matted to 18 x 22 inches, with 12 x 14-1/2 inch mat window. (36) (Box 385)
        - Anna Sokolow, I Had a Garden, (black shawl), 1940; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, trimmed and mounted on board, matted to 24 x 32 inches, with 14-1/2 x 19-1/2 inch mat window. (35) (Box 396)
        - Marian Van Tyl Group, Out of One Happening, (neg. 5306), 1944; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. Print trimmed to 10-3/4 x 13-5/8 inches, mounted and matted to 20 x 24 inches, with 11-1/4 x 13-1/4 inch mat window. (38) (Box 386)
        - Charles Weidman, Traditions, 1944; Gelatin silver print. Estate print. Embossed signature. 16 x 20 format with 13-1/2 x 16-1/8 inch image, matted to 20 x 24 inches, with 14-1/2 x 17 inch mat window. (69) (Box 386)
        - Charles Weidman, Atavisms (Bargain Counter), (ribbons), 1938; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print, matted to 22 x 28 inches,with 15-1/2 x 19 inch mat window. (40) (Box 390)
        - Charles Weidman, On My Mother's Side, 1944; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. Print trimmed to 13-5/8 x 18-3/4 inches, mounted and matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 12-1/8 x 18-5/8 inch mat window. (70) (Box 390)
        - Charles Weidman, Daddy Was a Fireman, (with Ray Hamilton), 1944; Gelatin silver print. Vintage, signed. 16 x 20 format print with 19-3/4 x 15-14 inch image, matted to 22 x 28 inches, with 19-1/2 x 14-3/4 inch mat window. (71) (Box 390)
      - Medium Prints and Mats (8 x 10 to 16 x 20 format prints, in mats 14 x 18 to 16 x 20 inches)